[ RAIN PATTERING ]
[ THUNDER RUMBLING ]
[ THUNDER CRASHING ]
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ CAR APPROACHING ]
[ TORMENTED VOICES ECHOING ]
Eight , eight , three , one .
[ CELL PHONE VIBRATES ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ GRUNTS SOFTLY ]
Eight , eight , three , one .
Okay .
Come on . Eight , eight , three , one .
Motherfuck . Okay .
[ EXHALES ]
[ CELL PHONE VIBRATES ]
Go away .
Eight , three , three , one .
Okay .
Oh , you 've gotta be kidding me .
Oh . Come on .
[ LINE RINGING ]
[ OVER VOICEMAIL ] Hi , you 've reached Bonnie Zane
with Greater Wayne Property Management .
I can 't come to the phone right now .
Oh , you gotta be fucking kidding me .
but please leave a message , and I 'll call you right back .
[ LINE BEEPS ]
Hi . This is Tess Marshall .
I 'm in town . I 'm at the house on Barbary .
And I 'm on the porch , and it 's pouring rain ,
and there is no key in the lockbox .
So , please , could you just call me back on this number ?
Thank you .
God damn it .
[ EXHALES ]
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ GROANS ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ DOORBELL BUZZES ]
Yeah ?
I 'm sorry , who are you ?
What ? Who are you ?
[ STUTTERS ]
This is 476 Barbary , right ?
I don 't know . Yeah , yeah . I think so .
You don 't know ?
No . I don 't live here . I 'm renting this place .
It 's the middle of the night . I don 't have it
in the top of my head , the address .
No , I 'm renting this place .
- What ? - [ THUNDERCLAP ]
I ... I 'm renting this place .
I ... I booked it on Airbnb like a month ago .
I booked it on HomeAway .
You 're fucking kidding .
Wait , wait .
Wait , are you sure you have the right place ?
Yeah , I ...
Yeah , my email says 476 Barbary . That 's here , right ?
And my code works for the lockbox .
I 'm supposed to be in here .
[ SIGHS ]
[ STUTTERS ] Did you try and call someone ?
Yeah . No one answered .
And you 're sure you have the right date ?
Look .
Yeah . I mean , it looks right .
Fuck . This is unbelievable .
What am I supposed to do ?
I don 't know . I don 't know .
Why don 't you ... Why don 't you come inside ?
And we 'll call these idiots .
[ THUNDER RUMBLING ]
[ TORMENTED VOICES YELL ]
- Uh , would you mind if I ... - Yeah ?
I need to use the bathroom .
Yeah , yeah , yeah . Of course .
It 's just down the hall , to your left .
Okay . I 'll be right back .
[ THUNDER RUMBLING ]
[ SIGHS ]
Would you mind pulling up your reservation confirmation ,
just so I can see it ?
In case I 'm some kinda weirdo , who 's broken in here to sleep ?
Yeah , yeah . No , it 's fine .
Let me just find my phone .
[ SIGHS ]
[ EXHALES ]
- Here . - [ YELPS ]
Jesus .
I 'm sorry . I didn 't know you were back .
- I was just getting my phone . - Sorry .
Here 's ... Here 's the thing .
Right .
Yep . That looks right to me .
Great .
Maybe I have a different number through HomeAway
than the one that you called ?
This is what I got .
- 303-5 ... 5 ... - 303-509 ...
Yeah , that ... That 's the same one .
Yeah . [ CHUCKLES SOFTLY ]
Listen , I don 't know what the protocol is for this .
Me neither .
BOTH : Um ...
I guess I 'll just find somewhere else .
- I mean ... - Yep .
Guess I 'm gonna do that .
Uh , I 'll let you get back to sleep .
I feel bad .
It 's clearly not your fault .
What are you gonna do ?
Just go drive around , looking for a hotel ?
I have my phone . Make some calls .
In your car ?
Yeah , I don 't think that 's such a good idea .
I mean , I don 't know if you got a great look at this neighborhood , but it 's not ...
I don 't think you should be sitting out there by yourself this late .
I mean , I wouldn 't do that .
Look , obviously , do whatever you want , but if you wanna hang out in here ,
where it 's dry , and there 's a lock on the door ,
I 'm totally fine with that .
Uh , here 's the Wi-Fi info ...
- Thanks . - if you need it .
Oh , by the way , I 'm Keith .
Tess .
Tess . That 's a pretty name .
Thanks .
Do you want anything ?
I think there 's some tea in the kitchen .
Um ... Want some tea ?
- I 'm okay . Thank you . - Okay .
Um ... Oh , shit , yeah . There 's ...
Somebody left out a bottle of wine here .
With a ribbon on it , like a housewarming thing .
And there 's some nuts here , too .
I 'm just saying .
I 'm okay .
Yeah . Yeah . Okay , cool .
Um , I 'm gonna have some tea .
I 'll just make you a cup .
[ CUPS CLINKING ]
Hi . Hi , I was just wondering , do you have any rooms available ?
Yeah . For tonight , that 's right .
Really ?
Okay , thanks .
Uh ... Shit .
You know what I just realized ?
The water is heating up , by the way .
- What 's that ? - There 's a convention in town .
What ?
Yeah , there 's , like , some huge medical thing .
I don 't think you 're gonna be able to get a room tonight .
[ SIGHS WEARILY ]
I can 't believe this .
[ SIGHS ]
All right . Here 's what I propose .
Why don 't you just crash here ?
Oh , no . I don 't ... I don 't think that 's ...
No , no , no . You take the bedroom , and I 'll sleep out here on the couch .
And then tomorrow , we 'll call these idiots .
Get our money back . Free stay for both of us .
[ GROANS ] Really can 't believe this .
I mean , I don 't know what else there is to do .
[ SIGHS ]
- I can take the couch . - No , no , no .
Call me what you want ,
but there 's no way I 'm sleeping in the bedroom
while a young lady is sleeping on the couch .
Blame it on my upbringing , but it 's not up for discussion .
Well , no offense ,
but I kinda have a thing about clean sheets .
[ OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING ]
You really didn 't have to do that .
Not even up for discussion .
Besides , I have a raincoat and you don 't .
- No , no , I got it . - Oh . No , no , no .
- You sure ? You sure ? - I can ... Yeah .
Okay .
[ CAMERA CLICKING ]
You left this in the bedroom .
Oh , shit .
Thanks . Good eyes .
I 'm gonna go wash up .
Yeah . Knock yourself out .
[ WATER RUNNING ]
Uh , hey .
Uh , the laundry 's still in the wash .
Um ...
But I thought , well , I 'm wide awake , so ...
So I , um ... It 's gonna be a bit now .
I thought I 'm gonna have some of this here wine .
But I didn 't wanna open it before you got out of the shower
because I noticed you didn 't drink your tea .
And , well , I totally get that , by the way .
I mean , you don 't know me , and this is a fucking really weird situation .
It makes total sense .
Um , but I thought that you might want some of this .
But if I opened it while you weren 't here , that ... that ...
Fuck , I 'm sorry . I 'm rambling .
Jesus Christ .
Um ...
I thought you wouldn 't want any if you didn 't see me open it .
So , I waited .
I 'm good , but you go ahead .
- You sure ? - Yeah .
Okay . Um ...
[ KEITH CHUCKLES ]
Um , it 's ... I 'd say you have about
an hour and change till the bedding 's done .
You gonna make it ?
I looked around for some clean ones , but I couldn 't find any .
What are you gonna do on the couch ?
Oh , I 'll be fine . Yeah . I 've slept on worse .
I 'm really sorry about all this .
What , are you kidding ?
It 's not your fault . You 're just as put out as me .
Do you want me to make you another cup of tea ?
- No . - [ BOTH LAUGH ]
You can watch this time .
I 'm okay .
So , um ...
What brings you to town ?
- Job interview . - Oh , yeah ?
Is it tomorrow ?
Yeah .
What 's the job about , if you don 't mind me asking ?
Yeah . It 's okay .
Um , it 's a research position for a documentary filmmaker .
Really ? Who 's the filmmaker ?
Her name is Catherine James .
Catherine James ?
I don 't know her .
Has she done anything I 'd seen ?
Uh , she made a movie about jazz last year ,
called Blue Easy .
Oh , I saw that .
You saw Blue Easy ?
I thought it was great .
Are you kidding ? No one 's seen that movie .
About the makeshift brass band ?
And there 's that scene with the kids on the rooftop ,
playing the Coltrane stuff ?
Yeah , it 's great .
I can 't believe you saw that .
I thought it was awesome .
What 's her new film gonna be about ?
Oh , it 's gonna be about this place . Detroit .
Like Detroit music ?
Oh , well , it 's gonna be about the artists
that have come here in the last ten years
and set up collectives and creative communities on the ...
Well , the edge of ...
Where the houses are basically free .
That 's pretty cool .
Do you know who you should interview for that ?
Who ?
Me .
Why is that ?
Because I 'm actually one of the founders of the Lion Tamers .
- You 're kidding . - No .
I mean , I 'm not , like , the guy , but I 'm one of the guys , yeah .
That 's insane .
- It is insane . - [ LAUGHS ]
What are you doing in an Airbnb ?
Don 't you guys , like , have a whole block or something ?
No , yeah . No , we do .
But we 're looking for a new space .
So , I 'm here for a week ,
basically just scouring this side of town .
Looking for our next little nest .
Oh , my God .
[ BOTH CHUCKLE ]
KEITH : It 's not a cliche I 've heard before .
TESS : Oh , come on . It 's such a cliche .
The guy who thinks love and control are the same thing .
And the girl who lets herself become ,
I don 't know , some kind of pet or something ?
Oh , my God . It 's so cliche and it 's so boring ,
and I can 't believe it 's happening to me .
Is it still happening ?
I mean , look at you .
You already got your new job lined up .
Mmm . Job interview .
I don 't have the job yet . I 'm not home free .
Look . There 's always gonna be people
that project some kind of dynamic onto us that serves them .
It 's up to us if we wanna play ball or not .
Is that my lesson ?
I don 't know . I don 't know .
[ CHUCKLES ] I just need to stop going back .
I keep going back .
Maybe that 's it .
Or maybe my lesson is that
guys will walk all over you as long as you let them .
Yeah . That 's my lesson .
I take issue with that statement .
Oh , yeah . That 's ' cause you 're a guy .
[ LAUGHS ] I mean , the world 's different for you .
Guys get to blast their way through life making messes .
Girls have to be careful .
- Elaborate . - Okay . Take tonight .
If I had been the one that checked in first
and you showed up late at night ...
What , you wouldn 't have let me in ?
Hell no . I wouldn 't have let you in .
Do you think I 'm crazy ?
But if I was dumb enough to let you in ,
you wouldn 't even think twice .
You would just march on in .
Hey , you just marched on in .
Yeah , because I had to . And it was scary .
What , do I look like some kind of monster ?
Not my point .
I get it . I get it . I mean ...
There 's a lot of bad dudes out there . And it sucks .
Look , are you gonna stay locked into some fucked-up toxic dynamic
that somebody else picked for you ?
Or are you gonna move on ?
Maybe find someone else .
Even if that means that you may get your heart
ripped outta your chest all over again .
Hmm . Why is it always the girls
who get their hearts ripped out in these things ?
Girls can rip . Trust me .
Okay , so now that it 's inside out ...
TESS : Right .
- Right ? That 's the first step . - Yeah ?
KEITH : Then , now you kind of go deep .
- You dive in . - No . [ LAUGHS ]
KEITH : Now , this ... Trust me .
This is the best way to do it .
No , you 're fucking with me . This is not how you do it .
KEITH : This is how you do it . This is the best way .
It never bunches up . It gets completely smooth .
You 'll thank me later when you 're lying
under a perfectly even duvet , here .
- So , if , but ... - Looks so dumb .
- KEITH : So , here ... - Right ?
Here is where I kinda need your help a little bit .
- Now that you 're here ... - Oh , my God .
- you have to be my assistant . - Right .
KEITH : If you wouldn 't mind ,
- grabbing the duvet ... - Okay .
and you kinda give me the two edges
- where my edges are ... - Yeah , sure .
where the two meet . All right , thank you .
- Okay . You got it ? - Thank you very much .
So , back up ' cause now it gets a little bit ...
- A little ... - My God . [ LAUGHS ]
- A little aggressive with the thing - TESS : Oh , my God .
But that is how you get the duvet in .
- [ EXCLAIMS ] So graceful . - That 's how you do it .
Are you usually this outta breath afterwards ?
[ PANTING ] The final ...
- Grab that edge there , please . - Mmm-hmm .
KEITH : Okay , and ... Yeah , yeah .
Wow .
Okay . Well , you are officially situated .
Yeah . I think that about does it .
KEITH : Yeah . [ LAUGHS ]
Okay , thank you for tonight .
Sorry for keeping you up before the big day .
Oh , no . It was fun . I ...
I liked it .
Yeah . Me , too .
Okay , there 's a couch that needs to be ...
Yeah . Yeah .
Put in gear here , so ...
I 'm so sorry .
Oh , don 't be . Don 't be .
I can sleep on anything .
Good night , Tess .
Good night , Keith .
[ SIGHS ]
[ DOOR CREAKING ]
[ SCREECHING ]
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ KEITH MOANING ]
[ KEITH WHIMPERING ]
- Keith ? - [ KEITH YELPS ]
[ KEITH YELPS ]
[ KEITH GRUNTS ]
Keith ?
[ KEITH WHIMPERING ]
[ DOOR CREAKING ]
KEITH : [ SOFTLY ] Help me .
[ KEITH CONTINUES WHIMPERING ]
[ SOFTLY ] No . No .
Keith ?
[ BOTH SCREAMING ]
The fuck !
Oh , I 'm so sorry .
[ STAMMERING ] What are you doing ?
Uh , I ... Um ...
My door was open .
And I didn 't open it , and I ...
You ...
And I didn 't know if you were up ,
and you were , like , making noises and ...
I was making noise ?
I 'm so ... I 'm so sorry .
I 'm just gonna ... I 'm gonna let you go to sleep .
You scared the shit out of me .
Did you open my door ?
No !
Yeah .
[ SIGHS ]
[ GROANS ] Oh , God .
[ GRUNTS ]
Shit .
Keith ?
[ FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ INDISTINCT CHATTER ]
WOMAN : Tess ?
TESS : Oh .
- Hi , Catherine ! - Hi !
- So nice to meet you ! - Nice to meet you , too .
Thanks for making the trip all the way out here .
Yeah .
[ INAUDIBLE ]
So , where are you staying while you 're in town ?
- Oh , an Airbnb . - Oh , that 's nice . Whereabouts ?
Uh , it 's in Brightmoor .
You know where that is ?
What ?
Yeah . You know it ?
[ CHUCKLES ] Are you kidding ?
Well , I mean ...
It seems a little rough , but ...
No , you shouldn 't be there .
- What do you mean ? - That 's not ...
An Airbnb in Brightmoor ?
Yeah , I mean , like ...
It 's a cute little house , but ...
Yeah , I suppose the neighborhood is a little ...
Tess .
Well , I did try and find somewhere else ,
but there 's , like , a convention in town or something ?
And I have a roommate , so ...
It 's a little complicated .
I guess .
Okay , well , just be careful , okay ?
- Seriously . - I will .
I 'm ... I 'm tough .
Good . Well ...
It was really nice to meet you .
Yeah ! No , I 'm excited .
I 'm gonna call you tomorrow , okay ? This is gonna be great .
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ ENGINE STOPS ]
MAN : [ YELLING ] Hey !
Hey , little girl !
[ TENSE MUSIC PLAYING ]
Hey !
Come here !
Hey , little girl !
Come out that house !
Go away !
[ PANTING ]
Yes !
I don 't know what ... I can 't see him anymore .
FEMALE OPERATOR : [ ON PHONE ] He left ?
TESS : I don 't know !
Can you just send someone , please ?
We don 't have any available units at the moment .
- What ? So nobody 's coming ? - Ma 'am , calm down .
As I said , we don 't have any available units at this ...
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ EXHALES ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ SWITCH CLICKS ]
[ DOOR CREAKING ]
[ DOORKNOB RATTLING ]
Shit .
[ SIGHS ]
Fuck .
[ OBJECTS RATTLING ]
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ DOOR CREAKING ]
[ OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING ]
Nope .
[ SIGHS ]
[ EERIE MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ SIGHS SOFTLY ]
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ SWITCH CLICKS ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
- [ KNOCKING AT DOOR ] - [ SHRIEKS ]
Keith !
[ LAUGHS ] What the fuck !
TESS : I 'm ... I 'm stuck down here .
Uh , do you have the key ?
It 's here , but I can 't open this !
KEITH : All right .
TESS : Right here .
[ BOTH GRUNTING ]
- Okay , you pull and I push . - Okay .
KEITH : One , two , three .
- [ WINDOW CREAKING ] - TESS : Okay .
- Are you okay ? - We need to go now !
What are you talking about ? Why were you in the basement ?
I got locked in the basement , and then there was this hidden area !
There was this room !
- [ BREATHING HEAVILY ] - There 's a hidden room ?
There is something bad going on here !
Tess ! Tess ! Relax ! Relax .
You 're okay , you 're safe .
You 're safe , all right ?
- You 're safe . - Okay .
I don 't ... I don 't think I am .
What 's down there ?
- What did you see ? - Okay ...
I was in the basement .
And then I found this hidden passageway .
And there was this room , and it was like a ...
Like a dungeon .
Like a dungeon ? What was in there ?
- There was a bed ... - Okay .
and a camera ,
and a bucket .
All right . Uh , so , there 's a bed and a ...
- What , a bucket and a camera ? - Yeah .
- I 'm just gonna go look . - No , no , no , please don 't !
There was , like , a handprint on the wall .
Tess , calm down , calm down .
You 're not making any sense , okay ?
So , there 's a room downstairs with a bed and a bucket in it ?
It 's a basement . It 's filled with junk , okay ?
It doesn 't sound that weird .
If you wanna go and look , suit yourself but I 'm going !
- Right now ? - Yes .
All right , Tess , no , no , no . Stop , stop , stop !
Just stop , stop !
- Move ! - Just stop !
Can you give me a moment , please ?
Can you just give me a moment ? Twenty seconds ?
Okay , I 'm sorry if I don 't seem like I 'm taking
whatever it is that you saw seriously .
I just ... I didn 't see it .
Okay ?
And I can 't just be running off in a panic
because there 's a room downstairs with a bed and a bucket !
Tess ? No , Tess ! Tess , wait , I 'm sorry !
I just ... I just want to see it .
You don 't even have to come with me if you don 't want to .
I 'm not going back down there .
That 's fine .
Can you just ...
Can you just wait up here
in case I get locked inside , too ?
Can you ?
I 'll wait .
[ SIGHS IN RELIEF ]
Just 30 seconds , okay ? Just wait here .
[ KEITH EXHALES ]
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING ]
Do you see it ?
KEITH : Yeah .
TESS : Okay , well , come back up now .
Keith ?
[ DOOR CREAKING ]
Keith !
[ UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING ]
Keith ?
[ DOOR CREAKING ]
[ OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
Keith ?
KEITH : [ FAINTLY ] Tess !
Keith !
KEITH : [ FAINTLY ] Help !
[ WHIMPERING ] Come up here , Keith !
KEITH : [ FAINTLY ] Help me !
Please !
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ BREATHING SHAKILY ]
Keith !
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
KEITH : [ FAINTLY ] Hey !
[ GATE RATTLES ]
[ TESS WHIMPERING ]
[ EERIE MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ WHIMPERING ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
Keith !
Answer me , Keith !
[ RUSTLING ]
[ EXCLAIMS ]
KEITH : Tess ...
Keith ! Keith ! Keith !
Why did you come down here ?
- Someone else is down here . - No , why ?
- Why did you come down here ? - There 's someone ...
[ WHISPERING ] Someone else is down here .
What ?
Someone bit me .
Okay . Okay . We need to go .
- We need to get out of here ! - No , don 't go near there .
- That 's where they were ! - No , that 's the way out !
- Come back this way . - No , please , stop it !
- Come this way ! - Stop it !
- We have to come this way ! - Let go off me !
- We have to come this way ! - That 's the way out !
- Someone 's down ... - Please stop !
I 'm not going back there ! I 'm not going ...
[ SCREAMING ]
[ THUDDING ]
- [ FLESH SQUELCHES ] - [ CREATURE GRUNTING ]
- [ TENSE MUSIC PLAYING ] - [ BODY THUDS ]
[ SCREECHING ]
[ UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING ]
Better get into what you gotta get into
Better get into it now No slacking , please
United Nations ain 't really united
[ SINGING ] And the organizations
Ain 't really organized
Rikki-tikki-tavi mongoose is gone
Everybody who read The Jungle Book
Will know that Rikki-tikki-tavi 's a mongoose who kills snakes
When I was a young man
I was led to believe there were organizations
That would kill my snakes for me
I.e. the church
I.e. the government
I.e. school
But when I got a little older I learned I had to kill ' em myself
[ PHONE RINGING ]
Yello !
WOMAN : [ ON PHONE ] Hey , AJ . I have David Stern
and Melissa Herberts for you .
Love it .
Guys , you 're on with AJ .
- Yo , what 's up ? - MELISSA : Hi , AJ .
DAVID : Hey , AJ . Uh , we need to discuss something
that 's just come through .
Cool . What 's up ?
MELISSA : So this is a bit of an awkward conversation ,
but there 's been a troubling development .
Okay , what ?
MELISSA : Apparently , Megan Maddox has contacted
the network through her lawyer ,
and she 's made a very serious accusation against you .
Really ? What 'd she say ?
She 's claimed that you were sexually aggressive
during the filming of the pilot ,
and she no longer wants to move forward if you 're involved .
She ... What ?
The network is taking this very seriously .
What does that mean ?
That means that at this time , they 're gonna start an investigation .
Wait , wait , wait . What about the pilot ?
Hold on . Wait a minute . This is crazy .
So , are we not picked up anymore ?
Well , like I said ,
they 're going to conduct an investigation , and then decide how to proceed .
An investigation ?
DAVID : AJ , I think , honestly , the most likely outcome of all of this
- is that even if the show ... - Yeah ?
Does go forward ,
it 's very unlikely that you will be involved .
MELISSA : No .
I 'm fired ?
DAVID : I think , essentially , that 's the most likely outcome .
That fuckin ' bitch .
Oh , my God . Oh , my God .
Wait a minute , you guys . Wait , wait , wait .
This is totally blown out of proportion .
MELISSA : Okay , I think it 's important to say
that it 's not in your best interest to go into details on this call .
The fuck does that mean , Melissa ?
DAVID : Okay , AJ , I think you just need to calm down ,
honestly , buddy . You can just relax .
This can 't be real . Just like that , I 'm out ?
Are you fucking kidding ?
I was the first to be attached to that !
She came on after me !
- DAVID : Okay , I ... - I recommended her .
DAVID : AJ , I think , honestly , you just need to calm down .
MELISSA : David , I think we should tell him the other thing .
DAVID : No , I think right now he just needs to cool down ...
What other ? What other ?
DAVID : It 's not important , AJ . You just have to relax .
No , no , no , fuck that . What other ? What else ?
MELISSA : There is gonna be a story tomorrow
in the Hollywood Reporter about this .
About what ? About me ? Are you kidding ?
MELISSA : The allegations are very serious .
Yo ... [ SCOFFS ] What 's she saying I did ?
Is she saying I raped her or something ?
DAVID : AJ , why don 't you just calm down , okay ?
No . What the fuck is she saying ?
MELISSA : Yes . She 's saying that you raped her .
DAVID : AJ , are you there ?
I gotta call you back .
[ SEAGULLS SCREECHING ]
MAN : [ SIGHING ] So , let 's assume
that the income we have for the year is what we 're gonna have at year 's end .
No new money coming in .
I think that 's pretty safe to say .
What do you anticipate your legal expenses to be ?
So , I talked it over with my lawyer ,
and we 're looking at two separate cases here .
There 's the defense against the charge , which is 100 % not true , by the way .
So , there 's that , and then there 's the countersuit for defamation ,
which I 'm 100 % gonna win .
I 'm gonna ruin this fuckin ' bitch .
How much ?
They said it 's probably gonna be , like , around 70,000 each .
So , 140,000 .
What does that do to me ?
Well , with your current rate of spending ,
that 's gonna put you at zero in ...
Three months .
Oh , fuck me .
[ LAUGHS ] Oh , my God .
You 've got some small income from your Michigan properties ...
But it 's your mortgage here that 's killing you .
Are you saying I have to sell my house ?
I 'm saying you 're gonna have to make some tough choices .
I could sell the Michigan properties .
Some of those make money , right ?
Yeah , but some don 't . You could sell those .
Buy yourself some time . But no more than a couple of months .
Those aren 't exactly hot properties .
I can 't fuckin ' believe this .
This is nuts .
Listen , AJ , I gotta tell ya .
What ?
At the end of this week , I 'm gonna give you your files back .
Cool . What 's that mean ?
I 'm going to suggest that you find alternate wealth management .
[ CHUCKLES ]
Oh , my God .
You 're dropping me too ?
[ INDISTINCT PA ANNOUNCEMENT ]
Oh , fuck me .
[ SIGHS ] Fuck .
It 's AJ Gilbride for Robert .
Gilbride . Thank you .
Robert , hey .
You see the article ?
Oh , it 's out . Yeah , insane .
Feel like I 'm sittin ' on the sideline ,
just watching this thing spiral out of control .
Robert , hang on . Wait , wait , wait .
I 'm just gonna put you on speaker .
Getting in a rental . Hold on .
You hear me ?
ROBERT : [ ON PHONE ] I hear you .
Uh , I was just saying , if I could just have ,
like , a conversation with her ,
I could probably nip this whole thing in the bud .
Absolutely not .
Under no circumstances are you to contact her .
[ SCOFFS ]
If I just call her and just be like ...
Listen to me .
There 's zero chance , at this point ,
that you calling her is gonna bring about
anything but more problems for you .
- Do you hear me ? - Mmm-hmm . Mmm-hmm .
Any communication goes through us from now on ...
Wait , I 'm sorry .
What do you mean you 're getting into the rental ? What rental ?
Uh , I 'm in Detroit . I rented a car .
You 're in Detroit , Michigan ?
Yeah . What ?
AJ , you aren 't supposed to leave the state .
[ SCOFFS ] Why not ? I 'm not under arrest .
I 'm allowed to travel .
This is not advisable .
You really need to be here in case there are developments .
" Developments ? "
You think they 're gonna arrest me ?
I think that is a very distinct possibility .
I think that flying off to another state is not a good look right now .
Well , Robert , I don 't know how to say this ,
but , um , unless you plan on taking me on pro bono ,
uh , I 'm gonna have to scrape up some money .
You know , I 'm not here on the lam .
I 'm not here on vacation .
I 'm here to do some fucking liquidating .
[ AJ CLEARS THROAT ]
May I help you ?
Yeah , I 'm an owner . I 'm here to pick up a set of keys .
Name ?
AJ Gilbride .
Oh , yeah . Bonnie said you 'd be coming .
Um ...
476 Barbary .
Fuck .
[ CAR LOCKS ]
[ SIGHS ]
The fuck ?
Fucking shit is this ?
[ URINATING ]
The fuck , dude ?
Hello ?
BONNIE : [ ON PHONE ] Greater Wayne Property Management .
Hey . Yeah , yeah .
Bonnie , it 's AJ .
AJ ?
Gilbride from ...
- Oh , AJ . Hi . - Right . Um ...
Is someone staying here at the moment ?
I don 't think so .
Well , someone 's here .
There 's a suitcase , and clothes , and shit .
Yeah , no . People are staying here .
I don 't ... I mean ...
We haven 't rented it out in a couple of weeks .
Well , do we know when the last tenants checked out ?
Do I have squatters ? This ...
I mean , are you saying that no one 's come by
to look at this place since the last tenants ?
Like , no maid or anything ?
The maids come to prep the houses before the arrival of the next tenants .
No new renters , no maid service .
That 's nuts . What if somebody trashed the place ?
How ... How would I know ?
Is the place trashed ?
No , Bonnie . The place isn 't trashed .
That 's not the point . The point is it 's ...
What kind of system is that ? It 's fucking idiotic .
I also don 't know why you 're so calm .
Have a nice day .
So , who the fuck is staying in my house ?
Hello ?
Dude .
WOMAN : [ ON PHONE ] AJ , I can 't hear you .
It sounds like you 're in a racecar .
AJ : I 'm washing my face .
What ?
I 'm washing my face .
Well , could you stop , please ?
Happy ?
Of course I 'm not happy .
I don 't know what to tell people .
What do you want us to say ?
I don 't know , Mom .
Just say she 's a lying fuckin ' bitch .
Oh , don 't talk ... Don 't talk like that .
What ? She is .
That 's not nice .
" Nice , " really ?
Ruining my career and reputation isn 't " nice , " either .
I think I 'm well within my rights to call her a " fuckin ' bitch . "
I know , sweetie .
I know you wouldn 't do those things .
When are you coming back home ?
It 's only a four-hour flight to Detroit .
You father and I want to see you .
Really ? Dad wants to see me ?
Did he say that ?
Oh , you know how he is . He 's just ...
- He 's upset . - [ CELL PHONE VIBRATES ]
Mom , I gotta go . I 'm getting an important work call .
- Okay , baby . I love ... - [ LINE DISCONNECTS ]
What up , faggot ?
Guess who 's back in town .
- [ ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ] - Could we just , like ,
real-talk for a moment , though ?
- Could we real-talk ? - Fuck , yeah , dude .
Okay , like , just , what the fuck actually did happen with you guys ?
No , dude . I 'm saying , like , you 're my boy , obviously .
I 'm gonna believe whatever you tell me .
- Right , right . - I gotta hear you say it .
No , I know , I know . I feel you .
' Cause I read the website .
I know what the fuckin ' Internet says ,
but , like , man-to-man , real-talk , what the fuck actually happened ?
Dude , I 'll be real with you , okay ?
- That 's all I 'm asking for . - Yo , yo , let me be ...
That 's the only thing I 'm asking .
Let me be real with you .
- We fucked . We did fuck . Okay ? - Right .
She just took some convincing , is all . That 's it .
Okay , but what the fuck does that mean , though ?
Like , I mean , was she like ... Did she say no ?
- Was she like , " No , stop ? " - I mean , at first .
But , like , I wasn 't like ...
" Come here , bitch . I 'm gonna rape you . "
Right .
It was like , in the beginning ,
she was like , " No ... " Whatever .
But , like ...
Then we started foolin ' around more , and then she was down .
- Like fuckin ' really down . - Right .
I 'm a persistent dude , right ?
I 'm like fuckin ' Eye of the Tiger .
- Yeah . Right . - You know ?
And she came around , and that 's it .
That 's what happened , straight up .
[ DOOR UNLOCKING ]
[ LINE RINGING ]
[ OVER VOICEMAIL ] Hi , this is Megan . Please leave a message .
[ LINE BEEPS ]
Hi , Megan . This is AJ . Uh ...
I 'm guessing you probably don 't wanna talk to me , but I , um ...
I just wanna say I 'm really , really sorry
if I did anything that night that might 've like ...
Offended you or ... [ SIGHS ]
' Cause you know , people can have different versions of the same thing .
And ... I 'm actually not even mad at you about it .
And I hope you 're not mad at me , ' cause I really ...
I really am sorry .
And if you call me back , I 'll apologize to you again .
So ...
Please call me back ,
and I 'll apologize to you again .
Okay .
[ GROANS ]
[ VOMITING ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ TOILET FLUSHES ]
Oh , shit .
Who the fuck are you ?
Oh , yes .
Okay .
" Tess . "
All right .
Fuck .
[ GRUNTS ]
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING ]
Hello ?
Fuck .
Somebody here ?
Hello ?
[ THUDS ]
Okay , here 's the deal .
I have a gun .
And I 'm gonna come down there and just
open up on whoever I see in about 30 seconds . All right ?
Or you can just come up here now , and I 'll let you go .
I 'm not fuckin ' around ! Who 's down there ?
[ SCOFFS ] Squat in my fuckin ' house ?
Huh ? Hide in my basement ?
I 'm a fuckin ' man . I 'll fuck you up .
Yes .
Last chance !
All right , bitch . Get ready to get fucked .
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING ]
What the fuck ?
[ LOUD THUD ]
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC BUILDS ]
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC STOPS ]
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES ]
Oh , my God .
" Can underground rooms be listed as square footage "
" when selling home ? "
Uh , " as for rooms in the house that aren 't finished ,
" like basements or attics , they should not be included "
" in the total square footage . " Fuck .
" Below-grade spaces , basements , dens , etc . ,
" do not usually count . "
Okay , " usually . "
" Even a finished basement can 't be counted
" toward the home 's gross living area , GLA , "
" but it can be noted separately in the listing 's total area . "
Oh , hell yeah .
Yeah , bitch .
Okay .
[ GRUNTS ]
All right .
This comes in at 9 by 12 .
Oh , gross .
Ten by 12 , that 's 120 . Three by 9 , that 's ...
- [ DOOR THUDS ] - Shit .
[ DOOR CREAKING ]
Oh , shit .
Yeah . Nice and easy .
Okay .
Oh , baby .
[ LAUGHS ] Oh , my God .
Nine feet .
Oh , my God .
[ LAUGHS ]
Jesus .
Yo , yo ! Anyone here ?
Okay .
[ CHUCKLES ]
What the fuck is this ?
Okay .
Yeah .
Here we go .
Oh , boy . [ CHUCKLES ]
Well ...
[ CHUCKLES ]
Ten ... 10 feet . Oh , my God .
What the fuck ?
Uh ... Hello ?
Hello ?
WOMAN : [ ON RECORDING ] by looking for indicators .
I like to let my baby determine how long he likes to nurse .
- Oh , God . - It 's important
that this process is relaxing .
Not just for the baby , but for me as well .
- What the fuck ? - This is a ...
- [ MEASURING TAPE RATTLING ] - [ TENSE MUSIC PLAYING ]
Hey !
- [ KNIFE CLATTERS ] - Shit ! Shit !
Who 's there ?
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ EERIE MUSIC PLAYING ]
Oh , shit !
Oh , shit .
Okay . Please . Oh , please .
Fuck ! Come on . Not again .
- Oh , shit ! - [ CREATURE GROWLS ]
[ CREATURE GROWLS ]
[ YELLS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
Fuck . Oh , fuck . Oh , fuck .
[ WHIMPERS ]
Shh ! Shh !
[ SOFT MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ BICYCLE BELL DINGS ]
[ CHILDREN LAUGHING ]
[ ENGINE STARTS ]
MAN 1 : [ ON RADIO ] Chief of Staff James Baker
says that the Reagan administration
has inherited the worst economy in 50 years .
This is Craig Tolliver , NTWN News .
WOMAN : [ ON RADIO ] Getting your kids to love
brushing their teeth is important , but it 's not easy .
And there 's so many name brands to choose from .
But how do you know which ones aren 't motivated ...
MAN : [ OVER PA SYSTEM ] Manager to checkout four for price check .
You findin ' everything okay ?
Plastic sheets ?
Plastic sheets ? We have some on seven .
Diapers and baby stuff ?
Infant needs are this way . Come on , I 'll take you .
So , how old 's your little one ?
Not here yet .
Oh , well , this is an exciting time .
Gonna take her to Mercy for the big day ?
Home birth .
Bless your hearts .
Plastic sheets .
What else do you need ?
You 've got a midwife , right ? She should 've given you a list .
No , it 's just me .
Oh , my word .
Diapers .
You are gonna want these .
The other ones , too big .
Do you have latex gloves ?
Yeah , I think , maybe .
Here .
Ah .
Now , some wet wipes .
MAN 2 : [ ON RADIO ] six-point-nine is Detroit 's
number one rock ' n ' roll destination .
Playing you the greatest songs of today .
Feel what radio was meant to be .
The ultimate musical experience is now .
106.9 , Detroit 's home of the rock .
MAN 3 : [ ON RADIO ] Are you in the market for a used car
but don 't have good credit ?
Detroit 's number one used car emporium , Martindale Motors
is here for you .
Bad credit or no credit ,
Martindale Motors will make sure you walk out of our lot
with a new set of wheels , and we won 't bend you over a barrel .
Martindale Motors is the Motor City 's number one used car dealership for ...
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ KNOCKING ON DOOR ]
DWP , ma 'am . Sorry to bother .
No bother .
We 've got some outages in the neighborhood ,
and I 'm just checking to make sure everything 's up to par .
[ WATER RUNNING ]
[ LOCK CLICKS ]
Thank you for your time , ma 'am .
Sorry for the intrusion .
So , everything 's okay , then ?
Looks fine to me , but do give us a call
if you get any issues .
Of course . Thank you .
You have a nice day now .
Hey , Frank .
How goes it , buddy ?
Doug .
Listen , pal .
I just wanted to tell you before you saw it for yourself ,
but , uh , there 's gonna be a sign in our yard tomorrow morning .
Sign ?
A " For Sale " sign .
We 're movin ' , Frank . Yeah .
I hate to do it . You know ?
But the wife thinks if we don 't do it now ,
we may not be able to get out this time next year ,
' cause , you know , neighborhood 's goin ' to hell , Frank .
You , uh ...
You plan on stayin ' ?
I 'm not goin ' anywhere .
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES ]
[ DISTANT SCREAMING ]
Okay . Who knows you 're here ?
Where the fuck are we ?
Does anyone know you 're here ?
No , no . Where the fuck are we ?
- I don 't know . - I gotta get outta here .
This is very , very important .
You need to stay calm .
You cannot freak out around her , okay ? Trust me .
- Okay ? - I don 't wanna be here .
Do you think I wanna fucking be here ?
- [ CREATURE GRUNTS ] - Okay .
You cannot get upset .
If you get upset , she gets upset .
" She ? " Who 's " she ? "
[ METAL CREAKING ]
What the fuck is that ?
[ OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING ]
What ?
Drink it .
Just fucking drink it .
What the fuck ?
[ CREATURE GRUNTS ]
[ GROANING ]
Do it .
Drink it .
Just drink it ! Get up !
Don 't you see ?
She just wants you to be her baby .
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ CREATURE GRUNTS ]
[ METAL GRATE OPENING ]
Oh , fuck .
[ TESS BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ CREATURE MOANS ]
CREATURE : Baby .
[ EXCLAIMS ]
[ GROWLS ]
[ BABBLES INCOHERENTLY ]
[ BABBLING CONTINUES ]
Oh , God !
[ CREATURE GRUNTS ]
Help me ! Please !
Fuck !
Wait , wait . No . Wait .
[ AJ GRUNTING ]
WOMAN : [ ON RECORDING ] A healthy baby
will generally need to ...
No ! No .
[ GRUNTS AND WHIMPERS ]
Fuck ! No !
This is perfectly natural .
CREATURE : Boop .
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ GRUNTS ]
Okay . Okay .
[ BREATHING DEEPLY ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
Oh , God .
WOMAN : [ ON RECORDING ] It can soon become
a pleasurable experience for the baby , and for you as well .
A little practice , you 'll find ...
[ AJ SCREAMING IN DISTANCE ]
AJ : Oh , fuck you !
WOMAN : [ ON RECORDING ] You can anticipate
when it may be getting hungry ...
[ AJ STRUGGLING ]
AJ : Oh , God . Fuck !
This is a time for us to bond .
To share this tender ,
- intimate moment . - [ CREATURE BABBLING ]
- [ AJ COUGHING ] - Your little one knows
how much they need
- more than you do . - [ AJ CHOKING ]
Don 't worry if feeding only lasts ...
No !
[ MEASURING TAPE RATTLES ]
[ CREATURE GRUNTS ]
[ TENSE MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ PANTING ]
No ! No ! No !
Oh , come on ! Oh , come on ! Oh , please !
Okay ! Okay ! Okay !
[ CREATURE SCREAMS ]
[ TESS GRUNTING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY ]
TESS : There 's someone else in there .
MAN : You 're free now . Come on .
There 's someone else in there .
I know it . I know she 's in there .
No , no , no . She has someone else in there .
We have to help him .
- [ FLY BUZZES ] - [ AJ COUGHS ]
You wanna go back in there ? Ain 't no helping him .
[ PANTING ] We can 't leave him .
You listen to me now .
You 're safe . You got out .
You should count yourself as lucky , you hear ?
You shoulda never went in that house to begin with .
That 's a bad place .
And she ain 't even the worst thing that 's in there .
Listen , you need to worry about you .
Now , I stay by the water tower .
It 's safe . Come on .
Wait , wait , wait ! No , no !
We can 't leave him . We have to call the police .
I ain 't got no phone .
She will kill him ! I need to help him !
And how you gonna do that ?
Come nighttime , she 's gonna come outta there ,
and she 's gonna come lookin ' for you .
She comes out at night .
So , if you wanna get goin ' , then go .
But don 't you come back .
And don 't you be around here when it gets dark .
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
- [ DISTANT SCREAMING ] - [ GASPS ]
Fuck ! Fuck !
[ CREATURE GROWLING IN DISTANCE ]
[ AJ MUMBLES ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ RADIO PLAYING ]
Do you have a phone ?
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO ]
- Fuck . - [ CAN RATTLES ]
- [ CRUNCHING ] - [ AJ GRUNTS ]
Jesus Christ .
Oh , my God .
- [ MAN COUGHS ] - [ TENSE MUSIC PLAYS , FADES ]
Oh , fuck . Okay . Okay .
[ COUGHS ]
Jesus Christ , man .
You scared the shit outta me .
You okay ?
Oh , my God .
Hey ! Hey ! Oh , my God .
- Officers , thank God ! - Ma 'am .
Take your hand off the door , please .
There is a man that is being held in a ...
Ma 'am , take your hand off the door .
Are you the one that called us ?
Yeah . I have been held prisoner for ...
I don 't even know how long , at a house near ...
[ POLICE RADIO CHATTER , STATIC ]
This is 72 , go .
OFFICER : [ ON RADIO ] We have a situation at the Center Board .
Copy that . Give me 10 .
You have any ID ?
No .
Are you listening to what I 'm saying ?
I have been held prisoner .
So , you don 't have ID ?
I don 't have anything !
I am not a crackhead . I am not a crazy person .
I am a woman who 's been held prisoner
and has escaped .
And I 'm telling you that there is a man in serious danger .
[ COUGHS ]
What do you want ? You want something ?
Over there .
- You want ... - [ COUGHS ]
Okay , okay . Okay .
- Um ... - [ COUGHING CONTINUES ]
Water ?
Water .
Okay , yeah ?
Good .
[ EXHALES ]
Fuck .
Listen , man . We 're gonna ... We 're gonna get out of here . Okay ?
I mean , I 'm gonna get outta here .
I 'm gonna get out , and I 'm gonna get help .
Gonna let everybody know what 's goin ' on down here .
That fuckin ' thing is gonna pay for what it did .
Don 't worry , okay ?
There are gonna be fucking cops swarmin ' this place real fuckin ' soon .
Trust me , man .
[ OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING ]
What do you want ? You want somethin ' else ?
I don 't know what you 're sayin ' .
What are you saying ? What do you want ?
Well , this is trash .
I don 't know what you want .
Man , you know what ?
Okay . How 's that ?
Yeah . This right here , okay ?
I don 't know what you 're saying .
Where 's my goddamn phone ?
TESS : You 're ... You 're gonna have to get this open .
Ma 'am .
If you don 't have keys , you don 't live here .
- We 're not goin ' in . - But just break it down .
There 's someone trapped in there .
- Come on ! - Hey , hey .
What are you doin ' ? Get away from there .
Get down here .
Can you ... Can you hear what I 'm saying ?
This is a crime scene .
She has killed a man already ,
and there could be someone down there getting murdered right now .
Ma 'am , there 's no one in this building .
No one 's being murdered .
And the only crime that I 've seen so far is you breaking this window .
[ SCOFFS ] What am I supposed to say to get you to listen to me ?
- Seriously , what the fuck ? - OFFICER 2 : Hey , Matt ?
We got shots fired on Midland .
Wait , wait . Wait .
- Are you motherfuckers leaving ? - Hey !
I 've had enough of you .
You 're lucky we don 't bring you downtown to sleep this off in jail .
Sleep this off ?
- Are you fucking kidding me ? - Joey , let 's move .
TESS : Wh ... Where are you going ?
- [ ENGINE STARTS ] - Where ... Where are you going ?
Come on , please ...
Please , please , don 't go ! Just ...
Come on ! I need your help , please !
Hey !
Oh , fuck .
[ GLASS BREAKING ]
[ WOMAN SCREAMING ON VIDEO ]
[ VIDEO STOPS ]
What is wrong with you ?
The fuck is wrong with you ?
Hey !
Hey , I 'm talking to you , you fuck !
Hey . Hey , hey , hey , okay .
[ CAR BEEPS ]
[ ENGINE RUMBLING ]
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING ]
No . No , no , no , wait ! Wait !
- [ GUNSHOT ] - [ MUFFLED GASP ]
[ ROARS ]
[ TENSE MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ ENGINE SPUTTERING ]
[ GRUNTING ]
[ ROARS ]
[ CREATURE MOANS ]
[ GROANS ]
[ WHIMPERS ]
[ UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ DOOR SLAMS ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ SMACKING FLASHLIGHT ] Come on .
- Hello ... - [ GUNSHOT ]
[ BODY THUDS ]
AJ : Oh , fuck . Oh , my God .
Oh , fuck . I 'm so sorry .
Hey . Hey , can you ... Okay .
Okay . I 'm so sorry .
Come on . We gotta get you outta here . Come on .
- [ SCREAMS IN PAIN ] - I 'm sorry ,
I 'm sorry , I 'm sorry !
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING ]
Okay , come on .
Looks like your car is fucked .
- She 's not there . - What ?
[ PANTING ] She 's gone !
What do you mean she 's gone ? Where the fuck is she ?
[ WINCING IN PAIN ] I don 't know .
What ? What are we gonna do ?
Do you ... You don 't have a car ?
Yeah , it 's right here , but the keys are in the tunnel .
I 'm not goin ' back in that shit !
Okay . I know . I know where to go .
Where ... Okay . Oh , fuck .
Okay .
How you holdin ' up ?
I 'm okay .
Okay . I think we 're almost there .
AJ : Okay .
Wait , what is this place ?
- He 's gotta be here somewhere . - Who ?
- ANDRE : Hey ! - [ AJ GASPS ]
Come here .
- [ TESS GROANS ] - Come on , man .
AJ : Come here . Okay .
- ANDRE : Right here . - Okay .
ANDRE : So , what happened there ?
Do you have any clean cloth or bandages or anything ?
ANDRE : Ain 't much clean in here .
I can 't believe she let you get this far .
What the fuck is she ?
She 's just a crazy lady livin ' in that house .
Since when ?
She 's been living there some 40 years now .
She was born there .
What are you talking about ? I own that house . Nobody lives there .
Boy , you might own that paper , but that 's her daddy 's house .
And he ain 't never left there , and she never left there neither .
He used to bring women down there .
And then he started making babies with ' em .
And babies with the babies .
And you make a copy of a copy of a copy ,
and you end up with something like that .
She got you real good .
I did that .
It was an accident .
Doesn 't matter . We gotta get you help .
Which way to get her help , huh ?
Y 'all need to just sit right here and wait .
I ... I can 't do that . This is my fault .
It don 't matter whose fault it is .
AJ : It does ! I hurt somebody !
[ SNIFFLES ] That matters .
I don 't know if I 'm a bad person .
But I might be .
I might be a bad person .
Or maybe I 'm ... I 'm a good person who just did a bad thing .
I can 't ... I can 't change what I 've done .
I can just try and fix it .
And that 's what I 'm gonna do .
I 'm gonna fix it .
ANDRE : You ain 't gonna do nobody no help
if you go out there and get yourself killed .
Now , right here , we 're safe .
And she 's gonna make it through the night .
Come morning time ,
then we can worry about takin ' her to town .
How do you know she can 't get in here ?
Shit . I 've been livin ' in this place more than 15 years ,
and she ain 't never came in this motherfucker .
- [ WALL CRASHES ] - [ CREATURE SCREAMS ]
[ ANDRE CHOKING ]
[ GROWLING ]
[ SCREAMS ]
AJ : Shit ! Oh , shit !
[ GRUNTING ]
Shit , shit , shit !
[ PANTING ]
Can 't get over the fuckin ' barbed wire .
[ CREATURE SCREAMS ]
[ CREATURE ROARS ]
[ TESS PANTING ]
- Wait for me ! - Fucking come on !
[ TESS WHIMPERING ]
[ CONTINUES WHIMPERING ]
[ TENSE MUSIC PLAYING ]
Your gun !
Oh .
Fuck !
There 's nowhere to go .
There 's nowhere to fucking go !
[ GROANS AND WHIMPERS ]
She wants us , she 's gonna get us .
She 's never gonna stop .
[ SOBBING ]
I can get away .
But you 're gonna have to slow her down .
- Hey ! - Don 't .
- [ SNARLS ] - Come get your baby !
[ GASPS ]
[ SOLEMN MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ BREATH TREMBLING ]
[ AJ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
Oh , fuck .
Oh , my God . Oh , my God . Are you okay ?
I 'm so sorry . I had no choice , you know ?
She was gonna kill us both , and ...
I had no time to think .
I fuckin ' panicked .
I didn 't ... I didn 't even let go . You started to slip .
There was nothin ' I could do .
You get it , right ? Okay .
You 're ... You 're gonna be okay . I gotcha .
I 'm saving you . Yeah , you 're okay .
[ HISSES ]
[ CHOKING ]
[ TENSE MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ AJ SCREAMING ]
- [ FLESH SQUELCHES ] - [ BLOOD SPLATTERS ]
[ BODY THUDS ]
[ BABBLES ]
[ BABBLING CONTINUES ]
[ WHIMPERS , BABBLES ]
Ba-ba .
[ TESS YELPS IN PAIN ]
I can 't .
[ BABBLES ]
I can 't go back .
Ba !
[ TESS EXCLAIMS IN PAIN ]
[ KISSES ]
Baby .
[ GUNSHOT ]
[ UPBEAT TRADITIONAL POP MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ UPBEAT TRADITIONAL POP MUSIC FADES ]
[ UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ UNSETTLING MUSIC FADES ]